Finding Aid for School of Natural Resources and Environment (University of Michigan) Records 1903-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Department of Landscape Architecture
  - Alumni Correspondence, 1917-1960
    - Smith, Charles, 1930-1952 (Box 55)
    - Smith, Robert, 1935-1953 (Box 55)
    - Stellhorn, Arthur, 1934-1952 (Box 55)
    - Stimson, Clara, 1926-1958 (Box 55)
    - Sweeney, Joseph, 1926 (Box 55)
    - Taylor, Warren, 1934-1957 (Box 55)
    - Wagar, John, 1941-1947 (Box 55)
    - Walp, J. Donald, 1935-1949 (Box 55)
    - Walz, Eleanor, 1939-1945 (Box 55)
    - Wasson, Groeso, 1932-1949 (Box 55)
    - Weldon, Ovid, 1935 (Box 55)
    - Wilcox, David, 1935-1955 (Box 55)
    - Wolbrink, Donald, 1931-1958 (Box 55)
  - Other Correspondence
    - Nichol's Arboretum, circa 1916 (Box 55)
    - Prospective Students, 1953-1957 (Box 55)
    - Chronological, 1967-1969 (Box 56)
    - Professor Chuck Cares, 1969-1979 (Box 56)
  - Accreditation
    - Accreditation Reports from SNRE
      - 1964-Winter 1979, 19 folders (Box 57)
      - Fall 1979-Winter 1985, 20 folders (Box 58)
      - Fall 1985-Fall 1991, 17 folders (Box 59)
      - Winter 1992-Winter 1999, 18 folders (Box 60)
      - Fall 1999-Fall 2000, 3 folders (Box 61)
    - Annual Reports, 1978-1993 (Box 61)
    - Reaccreditation Reviews, 1961; 1976-1989 (Box 61)
    - Self-Evaluation Reports
      - 1960-1961 (Box 61)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 61)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 61)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 61)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 61)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 61)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 61)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 61)
  - General
    - Faculty Meetings
      - 1958-1969 (Box 61)
      - 1975-1978 (Box 61)
      - 1990 (Box 61)
      - 2001-2003 (Box 61)
    - Michigan Workshop, 1982 (Box 61)
  - Student Papers
    - Dai, Katherine A. Marine Parks: Potentials of the Hawaii Marine Life Conservation District, 1978 (Box 61)
    - Dixon, David Lynn. Patient Care Sign Posting for the University of Michigan Medical Center, 1974 (Box 61)
    - Happel, Larry W. Urban Design Alternatives for Crystal Lakes, Ohio, 1973 (Box 61)
    - Hondorp, Craig. Enon Valley and Little Beaver Township: A Visual Analysis and Design Recommendations, 1976 (Box 61)
    - Hondorp, Craig and James McDonald. Relationships of Space and Land Use, 1975 (Box 61)
    - Jenkins, L., M.A. Miller, J. Przystup, and B. Rankin. Willis Community Study, 1971 (Box 62)
    - Lanham, Lynn. Image & Housing: A Comparative Evaluation, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Liss, Sara J. Public Restroom Facilities: Urban Necessity -- Pedestrian Amenity, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Maestrone, Mark C. An Arabian Gulf Culture and its Application to Landscape Architectural Design, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Mattison, Susan. Benton Park, 1977 (Box 62)
    - Moser, Roger. An Exploration of Potential Resolutions to Strip Commercial Development, 1974 (Box 62)
    - Mustonen, Erik. Historic Environment Preservation and Interpretation: With a Conceptual Application to the Keweenaw Area of Michigan, 1973; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Nemens, David Steven. Ellis Island: What it Was, What it Is, and What it Can Be (A Plan for the Development of Ellis Island as a National Historic Site, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Oates, Carl B. A Saginaw Riverfront Development, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Pieper, Louisa P. Lake Development: Problems and Possibilities, 1974 (Box 62)
    - Schervish, David W. Kercheval on the Hill: An Urban Redevelopment Study, Grosse Pointe Farms, Michigan, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Shiffman, Marcia Robins. Town Center Study: Highland Park, Michigan, 1976 (Box 62)
    - Straub, Peter. Whitehouse Nature Center Project and Plant Associations Project, 1974 (Box 62)
    - Stribley, Kathy. Looking Back on Public Housing: Deterioration and Change, 1976 (Box 62)
    - Tolbert, Gregory Lee. Urban Recreation: A Collective Effort, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Tracy, Darrel V., II The Role of the Landscape Architect in Southeast Alaska, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Troutman, Martin F. Site Evaluation Criteria for Mobile Home Parks, 1971 (Box 62)
    - Turner, Richard G. Plants in the Zoo: Their Use and Interpretation, 1974 (Box 62)
    - Willbach, Phyllis. A Redevelopment Concept for Grand Circus Park, Detroit, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Williams, Claire L. Renaissance Center, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Winter, Linda C. Michigan by Rail: Assessment of Scenic Quality, 1975 (Box 62)
- Properties Board
  - Annual and Special Reports, 1978-1984 (Box 70)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1983 (Box 70)
  - Meeting Agendas, 1980-1983 (Box 70)
  - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 70)
  - Properties
    - Hoyt Property -- Murray Lake, 1975-1986 (Box 70)
    - Ringwood Forest, 1980-1988 (Box 70)
    - Saginaw Forest, 1980-1990 (Box 70)
    - St. Pierre Wetland Preserve, 1975-1984 (Box 70)
    - Stinchfield Woods, 1977-1983 (Box 70)
- Archived SNRE Website
  The Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Natural Resources and Environment. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1997 as well as captures provided by Bentley Library archivists in 2002, 2004, and 2008. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Home Page
    - 1997-[ONGOING]
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - April 20, 2004, .ZIP file
    - May 9, 2008, .ZIP file
    - 2010-[ONGOING]
  - Related Materials: degree requirements, curricula, research, centers and institutes, 2010-[ongoing]